The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Is this... a breakthrough to Nascent Soul ?
With such momentum,
this person is sure to become strong in the future.
Sect Leader, will this person participate in the ceremony
so we can meet them ?
Could it... be an outsider
exploiting this blessed environment to breakthrough ?
They have so many Elders here
and none of them noticed until now ?
This is interesting.
Everyone stay calm.
In ten breaths,
I will capture this thief alive.
Let's see.
Is this your doing ?
All the elders of the Cloud Sky Sect are here.
Whoever he is,
he will die today.
Elder Liu !
Such spiritual energy fluctuations...
He isn't here to chat.
Who is this person ?
Wang Lin\NEarly stage Nascent Soul
Junior, who are you ?
Come.
Don't wait for the future love,
the soul between your eyebrows is already peaceful.
Senior,
save me.
She's mine !
Senior !
I asked the palm lines of time.
Sincerely entrust your love, don't waste time.
Wan'er knows that Senior has his own goals.
The cultivation path is extremely dangerous
but I hope that if you encounter danger in the future,
this formation can delay it for a moment.
I promised in my dreams
that from now on no one will block our path.
In the blink of an eye, I will change the world.
Killing Sun Zhenwei is easy.
But we have to wait
for my cultivation to be high enough so no one can oppose us
both in the Cloud Sky Sect and in Chu.
Sounds good ?
In all these nights of longing for the past,
deep in my heart
I believed that you and I
can cross the line between life and death.
We will overcome our doomed fate.
The night won't last forever.
Bitch !
Do you believe
Do you have a death wish ?
I'll kill you !
in the unbreakable reincarnation cycle ?
Die.
How dare you !?
Insignificant little newborn Nascent Soul,
you will pay with your life !
Die !
After seeing your longing eyes,
I want to keep them in my heart
to guard them
from the reincarnation cycle.
When I saw your beautiful face
This is my personal affair with the Cloud Sky Sect.
If anyone dares to intervene,
on our first meeting,
I believed
don't blame me for being ruthless.
If you wish to leave now,
I won't stop you.
Farewell then.
Let's go, quick !
that fate will never destroy our vows.
I have contacted the Ancestors,
they will be here soon.
Fellow cultivator, this is a misunderstanding.
There is no grudge between us.
We have treated Elder Li well.
We didn't know you were related to Elder Li,
hence the arranged marriage.
Now that the misunderstanding has been cleared,
we can stop here for now.
What do you think ?
Sun Zhenwei abused his father's position
to recklessly kill disciples.
He forced Wan'er to marry him.
You all pretended to be blind,
yet now you plead for mercy ?
Let's drag this fight,
the Ancestors are coming.
This kid,
is dead.
Senior,
the Cloud Sky Sect has 5 Late stage Nascent Soul ancestors.
We must leave !
I know...
I'm waiting for them to arrive.
Junior is acting up in our Cloud Sky Sect ?
Greetings Ancestors.
The Sect has lived for thousands of years,
but this is the first time someone dared attack
and kill my Elders.
Junior,
you won't have to wait for death !
Chen Bailang\NAncestor of the Cloud Sky Sect\NLate stage Nascent Soul
Wait,
Yun Tianzi\NAncestor of the Cloud Sky Sect\NLate Stage Nascent Soul
although he's Early stage Nascent Soul,
his artifact is too strange.
He's not an ordinary person.
Open the Cloud Sky Formation,
we must kill this demonic cultivator.
The thunder breaks the clouds, the sky becomes your cage.
Die !
As expected, the formation can trap his weird artifact.
Liu Fei, you joined the sect late.
You've never seen the Cloud Sky Formation in action.
It's a gift from a higher rank country.
It uses the elements to manipulate space
and trap the enemy.
Even a Soul Formation cultivator will be injured if trapped inside.
An Early stage Nascent Soul that relies on an artifact
is surely doomed...
This formation can manipulate space
to neutralize the Ji Realm.
He cannot use his lightning artifact anymore,
attack together now !
Senior, be careful !
Ancient God Restriction !
Did you say that
I cannot use my artifact anymore ?
Ancestors !
The Ancestors...
lost...
Who the hell are you ?
With your strength,
you must not be doing all this
just for a mere alchemist.
Please tell us your purpose !
I want the Cloud Sky Sect.
If we can catch the girl,
we still have a chance.
Looking for death ?
Hand over your Soul Blood
and I'll spare your life.
I have cultivated for more than 1300 years
and have never given anyone my Soul Blood.
If we fight you together,
you won't escape unharmed.
I'd rather die than be humiliated.
We will bet our lives !
Fine, don't blame me for it then.
Is this...
Divine Retribution ?
Even if you join forces,
I wonder
if can you withstand a tribulation ?
Every disciple Foundation Establishment and above,
will hand over their Soul Blood
or they will die.
Fine,
disciples Foundation Establishment and above,
hand over your Soul Blood.
The Cloud Sky Sect
is changing owners today...
Senior !
What's wrong ?
Wan'er, I need you to protect me.
Senior,
Your Nascent Soul...
why is it so weak ?
I failed to form my Nascent Soul
so I substituted it with my avatar
to temporarily gain Nascent Soul power.
Then...
Your cultivation will decline.
That's why you had to fight the Ancestors immediately ?
Senior...
Don't worry.
My failure is due to the time limit.
Now protect me, I must stabilize my cultivation.
Wan'er,
please make me some pills.
10 days later
Count the specks of time
floating down gently.
The carving knife in your hands etches out destiny.
Senior...
Forever lock away the scars
Wan'er, we have known each other for many years.
There are some things
that I wish to tell you.
of this mortal life.
This fleeting youth is a thing of the past.
I am not from the Burning Fire Country.
I come from a remote country named Zhao.
The flying bird could not escape the twilight
that fills the sky
with a myriad of colors.
The night-blooming flower cannot drink
the crystalization of the golden wind and the jade dew.
I asked the heavens who exactly
Noooo !!!
sliced open this world
to let the rain fall in.
I will refine the world
to make our palm lines say
that we will live forever.
Are you going to return to Zhao now ?
Yes,
because if I don't,
I'm unfilial.
You should come with me as well.
If I come to Zhao...
I will only be a burden.
I want to stay in the Cloud Sky Sect
so that I can improve my alchemy.
Only here do I have the right conditions to try to refine grade 6 pills.
That way I can be useful to you in the future.
Chu has many factions,
the Cloud Sky Sect is not safe,
you...
I have been in the Cloud Sky Sect for a long time
so I can take care of these things myself.
I will manage the Cloud Sky Sect for my husband.
I hope Seniors will take care of me.
Ancestors,
your status is very noble
so please don’t take the matter of the Soul Blood to heart
In 500 years,
Wan'er will return it to you.
To apologize,
I will make pills that will increase your lifespan
and gift them to you.
Each pill increases life by 50 years.
A pill that increases lifespan !?
Quick,
give it to me !
Did...
Did you really make this pill ?
I refined this pill,
but the materials were provided by my husband.
Rich spiritual energy...
a fragrant smell...
This is at least a grade 5 pill !
Elder Li refined this herself ?
I admire you !
You can become the Sect Leader ! I don't mind.
Elder Li is very proficient at alchemy.
You taking charge of the Cloud Sky Sect
is a blessing in disguise.
Little friend, you gave her our Soul Blood,
you can leave this place safely.
You can rest assured,
I will keep her safe for 500 years !
Teng Huayuan...
I, Wang Lin,
am coming back.
Wang Lin is pretty chill about his "failed" breakthrough, however it's quite a big deal.\NHere is the sequence of events:\N\N-Wang Lin has a Ji Realm cultivation that he unlocked by accident back when Teng Huayuan killed his parents. This type of cultivation is very strong but no known cultivators (neither alive nor in the ancient records of planet Suzaku) have ever reached a level above Nascent Soul with it.\N\N-Wang Lin reconstructs his original body thanks to the memories of the Ancient God and then goes back to Ma Liang's corpse to retrieve his Golden Core to continue to cultivate. At that point the Ji Realm is both in his soul and his new body.\N\N-After trying to reach Nascent Soul once and understanding that the Ji Realm is preventing him from advancing further, Wang Lin decides to use the Divine Path to create an avatar of himself (which is free from the Ji Realm as he has to cultivate from scratch with a new body) in order to merge with it.\N\N-The avatar cultivates up to the Nascent Soul breakthrough and then when it merges with the original body, the Ji Realm still prevents the Nascent Soul from forming naturally. In order to circumvent this limitation, Wang Lin undergoes the breakthrough only with his avatar, which reaches Nascent Soul without issues, and then puts his Nascent Soul avatar inside his Ancient God body to use its Nascent Soul cultivation instead of the original body's Core Formation cultivation.\N\N-With this convoluted method, Wang Lin is able to use the Ji Realm at Nascent Soul level but with a great cost of spiritual energy. This is only a temporary solution because now Wang Lin is completely stuck and cannot advance his cultivation anymore.
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.